National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty Records
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Petitions, 1999; nam_apap298-5; 0.75 cubic ft.
  - Stop Killing Kids Petition Binder - Belgium, Canada, United States [3 of 4], 1999; nam_apap298-5_3 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Stop Killing Kids Petition Binder - Belgium, Canada, United States [4 of 4], 1999; nam_apap298-5_4 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Stop Killing Kids Petition Binder - Netherlands, France, Spain [1 of 4], 1999; nam_apap298-5_5 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Stop Killing Kids Petition Binder - Netherlands, France, Spain [2 of 4], 1999; nam_apap298-5_6 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Stop Killing Kids Petition Binder - Netherlands, France, Spain [3 of 4], 1999; nam_apap298-5_7 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Stop Killing Kids Petition Binder - Netherlands, France, Spain [4 of 4], 1999; nam_apap298-5_8 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Stop Killing Kids Petition Binder - United States, France [1 of 3], 1999; nam_apap298-5_9 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Stop Killing Kids Petition Binder - United States, France [2 of 3], 1999; nam_apap298-5_10 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Stop Killing Kids Petition Binder - United States, France [3 of 3], 1999; nam_apap298-5_11 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Photographs, 1976-2001, Undated; nam_apap298-6; 1.95 cubic ft.
  Photographic prints of NCADP conferences and other events.
  - Aunt Mary, 1976; nam_apap298-6_1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - First Annual Meeting, 1978; nam_apap298-6_2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Halloween party, 1979; nam_apap298-6_3 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, 1981 August; nam_apap298-6_4 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Andy and Bill, New Year, 1982; nam_apap298-6_5 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Louisiana Execution of Joseph Cook, 1985; nam_apap298-6_6 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Open House Pictures, 1987; nam_apap298-6_7 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Bill Pelke Center, 1988; nam_apap298-6_8 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Photographs, 1988 December; nam_apap298-6_9 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Henry Schuwarzchild, 1989; nam_apap298-6_10 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Camilie Bell, 1990; nam_apap298-6_11 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - National Pilgrimage, 1990; nam_apap298-6_12 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Pilgrimage for Life, 1990; nam_apap298-6_13 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Photographs, 1992 April; nam_apap298-6_14 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Human Rights Day, Sydney, Australia, 1993; nam_apap298-6_15 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Bill Pelke/Andrews, 1993 July; nam_apap298-6_16 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Photographs, 1993 July; nam_apap298-6_17 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Board Retreat, 1994; nam_apap298-6_18 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Amgila Michelle Miller, 1994; nam_apap298-6_19 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Photographs, 1994 May; nam_apap298-6_20 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Photographs, 1994 August; nam_apap298-6_21 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Photographs, 1994 September; nam_apap298-6_22 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Photographs, 1994 October; nam_apap298-6_23 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Azi Kambule, 1995; nam_apap298-6_24 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Bryan Andrewmula, 1995; nam_apap298-6_25 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Marin Youth Hostel - Muder Victims Family for Reconciliation, Journey of Hope, 1995; nam_apap298-6_26 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Photographs, 1995 February; nam_apap298-6_27 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Photographs, 1995 October; nam_apap298-6_28 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Wilis Grove, 1995; nam_apap298-6_29 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Heath Wilkins, 1995; nam_apap298-6_30 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Rick Halperin, 1996; nam_apap298-6_31 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Missouri Conference, 1996; nam_apap298-6_32 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Photographs, 1996 January; nam_apap298-6_33 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Blank Postcards, 1997; nam_apap298-6_34 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Columbia Journey, 1997; nam_apap298-6_35 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Journey '97, 1997; nam_apap298-6_36 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Photographs, 1997 January; nam_apap298-6_37 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Gama Baralla, 1998; nam_apap298-6_38 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Capital Cards - Patrick Leahy, 1998; nam_apap298-6_39 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - William Lacy Clay, 1998; nam_apap298-6_40 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Conference Workshop - St. Louis, 1998; nam_apap298-6_41 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Tanya Cropper, 1998; nam_apap298-6_42 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Father Pat Delahanty, 1998; nam_apap298-6_43 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Jotaka Eaddy and Liletha Darideu, 1998; nam_apap298-6_44 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Danny Glove, 1998; nam_apap298-6_45 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Steve Hawkins and Danny Glove, 1998; nam_apap298-6_46 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Marietta Jaegar and Helen Prejean in Texas, 1998; nam_apap298-6_47 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Tonyo McClay, 1998; nam_apap298-6_48 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Missouri Summit Meeting, 1998; nam_apap298-6_49 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Missouri Summit Meeting, 1998; nam_apap298-6_50 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - New Orleans, Louisiana, 1998 June 19; nam_apap298-6_51 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Photographs, 1998 July; nam_apap298-6_52 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Postcard to Bill, 1998; nam_apap298-6_53 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Texas, 1998; nam_apap298-6_54 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Ron Tubak - Missouri Summit Meeting, 1998; nam_apap298-6_55 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Rev. Reynolds Thomas and Ms. Vera Thomas, 1998; nam_apap298-6_56 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Action, 1999; nam_apap298-6_57 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Annual Conference - New Orleans, LA, 1999; nam_apap298-6_58 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Annual Conference - Pittsburg, PA, 1999; nam_apap298-6_59 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Annual Conference - Pittsburg, PA, 1999; nam_apap298-6_60 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Annual Conference - St. Louis, Missouri, 1999; nam_apap298-6_61 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Annual Conference - St. Louis, Missouri, 1999; nam_apap298-6_62 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Annual Conference - Washington, DC, 1999; nam_apap298-6_63 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Annual Fast and Vigil - Washington, DC, 1999; nam_apap298-6_64 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Oscar Arias, 1999; nam_apap298-6_65 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Harry A. Blackman, Supreme Court Justice, 1999; nam_apap298-6_66 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Blue April, April Black, 1999; nam_apap298-6_67 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Blue Individuals April 1999, nam_apap298-6_68 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - The Board at Work, 1999; nam_apap298-6_69 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Board of Directors and Staff, 1999; nam_apap298-6_70 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Julian Bond, 1999; nam_apap298-6_71 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - William J. Brennan, Supreme Court Justice, 1999; nam_apap298-6_72 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Rosalyn Carter and Sister Helen Prejean, 1999; nam_apap298-6_73 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Ruben Hurricane Carter, 1999; nam_apap298-6_74 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Celebrities in Action, 1999; nam_apap298-6_75 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Ernie Chambers, 1999; nam_apap298-6_76 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Conference '99 Protest Rally, 1999; nam_apap298-6_77 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Contact Sheets, 1999; nam_apap298-6_78 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Mario Cuomo, 1999; nam_apap298-6_79 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Marshall Dayan, 1999; nam_apap298-6_80 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Steve Earle at Frankfort Rally, 1999; nam_apap298-6_81 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Film Negatives, 1999; nam_apap298-6_82 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - General Photo Files, 1999 April; nam_apap298-6_83 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Bianca Jagger, 1999; nam_apap298-6_84 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Javeboo Hall and Jeff Garis, 1999; nam_apap298-6_85 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Individuals (unlabeled), 1999; nam_apap298-6_86 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - International Abolitionist Movement, 1999; nam_apap298-6_87 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Interns, 1999; nam_apap298-6_88 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Journey of Hope - Murder Victims Families for Reconciliation, 1999; nam_apap298-6_89 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Journey of Hope Tennessee, 1999; nam_apap298-6_90 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Azi Kambule, 1999; nam_apap298-6_91 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Celia McWee, Protest Rally, 1999; nam_apap298-6_92 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - National Activism, 1999; nam_apap298-6_93 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Notes Found with Photographs, 1999; Undated; nam_apap298-6_94 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Photo Negatives, 1999; nam_apap298-6_95 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Photographs, 1999; nam_apap298-6_96 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Photographs, 1999 April; nam_apap298-6_97 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Pilgrimage for Abolition, 1999; nam_apap298-6_98 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Pilgrimage for Abolition, 1999; nam_apap298-6_99 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Sister Helen Prejean, 1999; nam_apap298-6_100 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Claudia Roth, Chairwomen of the Committee on Human Rights and Humanitarian Aid of the German Parliament, 1999; nam_apap298-6_101 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Diana Rust - Tiemey, 1999; nam_apap298-6_102 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Symbolic Pictures, 1999; nam_apap298-6_103 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Desmond Tutu, 1999; nam_apap298-6_104 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Abe W. and Desmond Tutu, 1999; nam_apap298-6_105 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Bad Welch, 1999; nam_apap298-6_106 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - George White, Bill Pelke, Sam Reese Sheppard, Abe Bonowitz, 1999 April; nam_apap298-6_107 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Dennis Williams, 1999; nam_apap298-6_108 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Youth Activism - NCADP College Tour, 1999; nam_apap298-6_109 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Howard Zehr, 1999; nam_apap298-6_110 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Chile Conference, 2000; nam_apap298-6_111 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Gary Graham Execution and Funeral, 2000; nam_apap298-6_112 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - North Carolina Rally and March, 2001; nam_apap298-6_113 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Photographs, 2001 October; nam_apap298-6_114 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Abolitionists Converged, Undated; nam_apap298-6_115 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - "Actual Innocence", Undated; nam_apap298-6_116 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - R. Adams, Undated; nam_apap298-6_117 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Adjoa Aiyetoro, Undated; nam_apap298-6_118 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Alabamians Against the Death Penalty, Undated; nam_apap298-6_119 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Alan and Lindsay, Undated; nam_apap298-6_120 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Autographed Portraits, Illegible, Undated; nam_apap298-6_121 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Hugo Bedau, Undated; nam_apap298-6_122 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Book Signing: Hele Prejean, William Styron, Rose Styron, Undated; nam_apap298-6_123 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Susan Boster, Undated; nam_apap298-6_124 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Justice Brennan, Sister Helen Prejean, Susan Sarender, Undated; nam_apap298-6_125 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Bruderhof Community, Undated; nam_apap298-6_126 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Dick Burr and Leigh Dingerson, Undated; nam_apap298-6_127 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Jeb Bash, Signed portrait, Undated; nam_apap298-6_128 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - C. Byers, Undated; nam_apap298-6_129 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Johnny Cochran and Steve Hawkins, Undated; nam_apap298-6_130 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Steve Dean, Governor George Ryan, Mike Farrell, Undated; nam_apap298-6_131 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Death Penalty in the Arts Plenany, Undated; nam_apap298-6_132 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Delegation at European Parliament, Undated; nam_apap298-6_133 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Leigh Dengesen, Bob Gross, Undated; nam_apap298-6_134 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Awi Detruico, Undated; nam_apap298-6_135 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Micki Dickoff, Undated; nam_apap298-6_136 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Leigh Dingeraon, Undated; nam_apap298-6_137 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Totaka Eaddy and Suemyra Shah, Undated; nam_apap298-6_138 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Steve Earie, Undated; nam_apap298-6_139 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - David Elliot, Communications Director, Undated; nam_apap298-6_140 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Film Negatives, Undated; nam_apap298-6_141 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Film Negatives, Undated; nam_apap298-6_142 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - K. Fox, Undated; nam_apap298-6_143 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Stephanie Gibson, Undated; nam_apap298-6_144 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Danny Glove, Undated; nam_apap298-6_145 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Rick Halperin, Marietta Yaeger, Bill Pelke, Undated; nam_apap298-6_146 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Steve Hawkins, Undated; nam_apap298-6_147 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Steve Hawkins and Rev. Jessie Jackson, Undated; nam_apap298-6_148 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Steve Hawkins and Governor Ryan, Undated; nam_apap298-6_149 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Steve Hawkins and Melody Smith, Undated; nam_apap298-6_150 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Maria Hines, Undated; nam_apap298-6_151 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Houston, Undated; nam_apap298-6_152 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Individuals Speaking, Undated; nam_apap298-6_153 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Joe Ingle, Undated; nam_apap298-6_154 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Rev. Jessie Jackson, Undated; nam_apap298-6_155 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Sunny Jacobs, Paula E., Undated; nam_apap298-6_156 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Jay Jacobson, Rachel Key, Undated; nam_apap298-6_157 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Jeu, Tim Spann, Nick, Carol Byers, John Mosher, Undated; nam_apap298-6_158 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Pope John Paul ll, Undated; nam_apap298-6_159 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - "Jotaka's Picture", Undated; nam_apap298-6_160 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Ken-e, Undated; nam_apap298-6_161 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Coretta Scott King, Undated; nam_apap298-6_162 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Jessica Landry-Baters, Youth Activist Awardee, Undated; nam_apap298-6_163 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Laura and Jessica, Undated; nam_apap298-6_164 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Brenda Lewis, Undated; nam_apap298-6_165 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Brenda Lewis and Frank Ballance, Undated; nam_apap298-6_166 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Los Angeles White Supremacist, Undated; nam_apap298-6_167 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Rev. Joe Loweny, Undated; nam_apap298-6_168 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Sam Moretta, Undated; nam_apap298-6_169 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Migel Martinez (TX) - Juvenile, 17 yr, Undated; nam_apap298-6_170 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Terry Mooney (OK) - Juvenile, 16 yr, Undated; nam_apap298-6_171 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - National Coalition members, Undated; nam_apap298-6_172 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Negatives with CD, Undated; nam_apap298-6_173 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Negatives with CD, Undated; nam_apap298-6_174 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Helen Pajama, Undated; nam_apap298-6_175 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Paula E., Undated; nam_apap298-6_176 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Bill Pelke, Undated; nam_apap298-6_177 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Pittsburgh, Undated; nam_apap298-6_178 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Photograph of man during trial, Undated; nam_apap298-6_179 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Photographs, Undated; nam_apap298-6_180 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Photographs, Undated; nam_apap298-6_181 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Photographs, Undated; nam_apap298-6_182 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Photographs, Undated; nam_apap298-6_183 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Photographs, Undated; nam_apap298-6_184 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Photographs, Undated; nam_apap298-6_185 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Photographs, Undated; nam_apap298-6_186 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, Undated; nam_apap298-6_187 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, Undated; nam_apap298-6_188 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, Undated; nam_apap298-6_189 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Photographs, Undated; nam_apap298-6_190 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Photographs, Undated; nam_apap298-6_191 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Photographs, Undated; nam_apap298-6_192 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Photographs, Undated; nam_apap298-6_193 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Photographs, Undated; nam_apap298-6_194 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Photographs, Undated; nam_apap298-6_195 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Photographs, Undated; nam_apap298-6_196 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, Undated; nam_apap298-6_197 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, Undated; nam_apap298-6_198 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, Undated; nam_apap298-6_199 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Photographs used for publications, Undated; nam_apap298-6_200 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Phyllis Patraut, Undated; nam_apap298-6_201 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Postcard to Faye Chappell, Undated; nam_apap298-6_202 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Press Interview on night of Joseph O' Dell's execution in Virginia, 1997; nam_apap298-6_203 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Sister Helen Prejean, Undated; nam_apap298-6_204 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Sister Helen Prejean, Lisa Radalet, Undated; nam_apap298-6_205 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Sister Helen Prejean, Bryan Stevens, Mike Fawell, Undated; nam_apap298-6_206 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Rachel, Bill and Judy, Undated; nam_apap298-6_207 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - K+H Robinson, Undated; nam_apap298-6_208 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - D. Routerice, Undated; nam_apap298-6_209 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Sally P, Carol D, Sally Peck, Undated; nam_apap298-6_210 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Susan Sarandon, Tim Robbins, Sister Helen Prejean and Sister Theresa Bangert, Undated; nam_apap298-6_211 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Sam Sheppard, Undated; nam_apap298-6_212 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - St. Louis, Undated; nam_apap298-6_213 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - "Symboliz", Undated; nam_apap298-6_214 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Desmond Tutu, Undated; nam_apap298-6_215 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Radio Vaticana - 35 millimeter slide, Undated; nam_apap298-6_216 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Sue Vanghu and Steve Hawkins, Undated; nam_apap298-6_217 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Christie Webb, Undated; nam_apap298-6_218 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Bud Welch, Undated; nam_apap298-6_219 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Charlie Wilton, Undated; nam_apap298-6_220 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - X-Mas March, Rome, Undated; nam_apap298-6_221 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Marietta Yaeger, Leno Rose Andir, Undated; nam_apap298-6_222 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Audio, 1981-2005, Undated; nam_apap298-7; 0.35 cubic ft.
  Alphabetical by the creator's last name or title of material.
  Recorded cassette tapes and one compact disc with recordings of NCADP annual conferences, radio shows, and executions.
  - Alive Todaym Death Row Callins, USA - A.J. Bannister to Steven Hawkins, 1997 July 11; nam_apap298-7_1 (Cassette 1)
  - Jim Beardon, R. A. H., 1992; nam_apap298-7_2 (Cassette 2)
  - Capital Punishment: A Thirst for Blood or Justice, Attorney Rod Jones; Radio Segments - "Justice Blinded" Series KZYX/KMUD Public Radio, Undated; nam_apap298-7_3 (Cassette 3)
  - Coalition for the Death Penalty, 1981 October 4; nam_apap298-7_4 (Cassette 4)
  - Judy C. Cumbee "Bringin' Abolition Day!" [commercial music], Undated; nam_apap298-7_5 (Cassette 5)
  - Death Penalty Features KPBX Spokane 2-24, 25, 26-87, Undated; nam_apap298-7_6 (Cassette 6)
  - Death Penalty - Texas "Primetime" ch. 12 Phoenix Arizona, 9:45 pm, 1997 February 26; nam_apap298-7_7 (Cassette 7)
  - L. C. Dorsey, Saturday Afternoon, Undated; nam_apap298-7_8 (Cassette 8)
  - Ebenezer Baptist Church Atlanta, NCADP Program Parts 1, 2, 1990 May 18; nam_apap298-7_9 (Cassette 9)
  - Ebenezer Baptist Church Atlanta, NCADP Program Parts 3, 4, 1990 May 18; nam_apap298-7_10 (Cassette 10)
  - Execution - Randy Greenawalt, 1997 January 23; nam_apap298-7_11 (Cassette 11)
  - Execution - Jimmie Wayne Jeffers, Arizona State Prison, 1995 September 13; nam_apap298-7_12 (Cassette 12)
  - From Death Row: This is Mumia Abu-Jamal, Undated; nam_apap298-7_13 (Cassette 13)
  - Dr. Jim Grigson, Psychiatrist Texas Death Row, Undated; nam_apap298-7_14 (Cassette 14)
  - Ben Jealous, 30 minute interview with Joseph Payne on death row in Virginia and his lawyer Paul Khoury, 1996 October 28; nam_apap298-7_15 (Cassette 15)
  - John and Ken Show, 3-4 pm KFI AM 640/KOST 103 FM, 1995 December 5; nam_apap298-7_16 (Cassette 16)
  - National Public Radio: "All Things Considered" on medical participation report (breach of trust), 1994 April 3; nam_apap298-7_17 (Cassette 17)
  - National Public Radio: William Brennan, Supreme Court Justice, 1987; nam_apap298-7_18 (Cassette 18)
  - National Public Radio: Loyal Garner Jr. case, 1988 August 10; nam_apap298-7_19 (Cassette 19)
  - National Public Radio: Diane Rhems, Mikel Gilmore new book, Shot in the Heart, 1994 May 25; nam_apap298-7_20 (Cassette 20)
  - National Public Radio: The Diane Rhems Show, The Death Penalty, 2005 December 5; nam_apap298-7_21 (Cassette 21)
  - NCADP National Conference 1981 Tape 2, 1981 September 26-27; nam_apap298-7_22 (Cassette 22)
  - NCADP National Conference 1981 Tape 3, 1981 September 26-27; nam_apap298-7_23 (Cassette 23)
  - NCADP National Conference 1981 Tape 4, 1981 September 26-27; nam_apap298-7_24 (Cassette 24)
  - NCADP National Conference 1981 Tape 5, 1981 September 26-27; nam_apap298-7_25 (Cassette 25)
  - NCADP National Conference 1981 Tape 6, 1981 September 26-27; nam_apap298-7_26 (Cassette 26)
  - NCADP National Conference 1990 - Rev. Rodney Young & Robert R. Bryan: Race, Politics and Death in the 90s, 1990 November 9; nam_apap298-7_27 (Cassette 27)
  - NCADP National Conference 1990 - Rev. Rodney Young & Robert R. Bryan: Race, Politics and Death in the 90s, 1990 November 9; nam_apap298-7_28 (Cassette 28)
  - NCADP National Conference 1990 - Rev. Rodney Young & Robert R. Bryan: Race, Politics and Death in the 90s, 1990 November 9; nam_apap298-7_29 (Cassette 29)
  - NCADP National Conference 1990 - Changing the Focus: A Realistic Look at Crime and Offenders, 1990 November 10; nam_apap298-7_30 (Cassette 30)
  - NCADP National Conference 1990 - Changing the Focus: A Realistic Look at Crime and Offenders, 1990 November 10; nam_apap298-7_31 (Cassette 31)
  - NCADP National Conference 1990 - Changing the Focus: A Realistic Look at Crime and Offenders, 1990 November 10; nam_apap298-7_32 (Cassette 32)
  - NCADP National Conference 1990 - Preventing Reinstatement: Jonathon Gradess, 1990 November 10; nam_apap298-7_33 (Cassette 33)
  - NCADP National Conference 1990 - Preventing Reinstatement: Jonathon Gradess, 1990 November 10; nam_apap298-7_34 (Cassette 34)
  - NCADP National Conference 1990 - Preventing Reinstatement: Jonathon Gradess, 1990 November 10; nam_apap298-7_35 (Cassette 35)
  - NCADP National Conference 1990 - Taking Action: The Role of Civil Disobedience for Social Change, 1990 November 10; nam_apap298-7_36 (Cassette 36)
  - NCADP National Conference 1990 - Taking Action: The Role of Civil Disobedience for Social Change, 1990 November 10; nam_apap298-7_37 (Cassette 37)
  - NCADP National Conference 1990 - Working With Victims' Families: Adele Shank, 1990 November 10; nam_apap298-7_38 (Cassette 38)
  - NCADP National Conference 1990 - Working With Victims' Families: Adele Shank, 1990 November 10; nam_apap298-7_39 (Cassette 39)
  - NCADP National Conference 1990 - Rev. Dr. Joseph Lowery, Robert R. Bryan, 1990 November 11; nam_apap298-7_40 (Cassette 40)
  - NCADP National Conference 1990 - Rev. Dr. Joseph Lowery, Robert R. Bryan, 1990 November 11; nam_apap298-7_41 (Cassette 41)
  - NCADP National Conference 1990 - Rev. Dr. Joseph Lowery, Robert R. Bryan Closing Address, 1990 November 11; nam_apap298-7_42 (Cassette 42)
  - NCADP National Conference 1990 - Real Victims, Real Responses, 1990 November 11; nam_apap298-7_43 (Cassette 43)
  - NCADP National Conference 1990 - Real Victims, Real Responses, 1990 November 11; nam_apap298-7_44 (Cassette 44)
  - New Voices - 247, Public Interest Video Network, 1990 December 10; nam_apap298-7_45 (Cassette 45)
  - News Broadcast "Death Penalty" 8:17 PM, 1997 February 26; nam_apap298-7_46 (Cassette 46)
  - Prison the Last Option, Background Briefing - Radio National Australia, 1992 March; nam_apap298-7_47 (Cassette 47)
  - Geoffrey Robertson, QC. Death Penalty, Sydney, 1994 February; nam_apap298-7_48 (Cassette 48)
  - The Rope, the Chair, the Needle MD SDV TM, 1998 February 3; nam_apap298-7_49 (Cassette 49)
  - Jane Stroessner, "Never Say Die", Undated; nam_apap298-7_50 (Cassette 50)
  - Darby J. Tillis, "Death to Life" [commercial music], 2002; nam_apap298-7_51 (Cd 1)
  - Lem Davis Tubble, Jr., interview from Mecklemberg prison, 1996 November 23; nam_apap298-7_52 (Cassette 51)
  - Alton Waye, 10 PM, 1989 August 30; nam_apap298-7_53 (Cassette 52)
  - Howard Zinn: Stop the Death Penalty, Harvard University, Cambridge, MA, 1996 March 11; nam_apap298-7_54 (Cassette 53)
- Video, 1985-2005; nam_apap298-8; 5.40 cubic ft.